<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Patterns on Infusion</title>
    <link>https://thepaciellogroup.github.io/infusion/patterns/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Patterns on Infusion</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://thepaciellogroup.github.io/infusion/patterns/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Installation and configuration</title>
      <link>https://thepaciellogroup.github.io/infusion/patterns/installation/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thepaciellogroup.github.io/infusion/patterns/installation/</guid>
      <description>To use Albos in a production environment, you need to include albos.min.js in your HTML document. The easiest way is to use our CDN version, but you can also use NPM or clone the repository locally.
Get the file Link to the file using our CDN If you don&amp;rsquo;t mind hosting from an external location, you can simply paste this line of code before your closing &amp;lt;/body&amp;gt;:
&amp;lt;script src=&amp;quot;cdn/albos.min.js&amp;quot; /&amp;gt;  Using NPM To host NPM yourself and it include it as a depency in other projects, install the Albos package using NPM:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Setup</title>
      <link>https://thepaciellogroup.github.io/infusion/patterns/setup/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thepaciellogroup.github.io/infusion/patterns/setup/</guid>
      <description>By now, you should have followed the instructions. You should have Hugo and Node installed, and a local copy of a forked version of Infusion. You should also have run npm install in the root of that codebase.
&amp;ldquo;Cleaning&amp;rdquo; the content folder Before you can start writing documentation, there are a few things still to do in order to get set up. At the moment, your version of Infusion is a facsimile of the original, containing all the content you&amp;rsquo;re reading right now.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Serving</title>
      <link>https://thepaciellogroup.github.io/infusion/patterns/serving/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thepaciellogroup.github.io/infusion/patterns/serving/</guid>
      <description>Serving locally While you&amp;rsquo;re creating content for your project, you&amp;rsquo;ll probably want to see what the finished product looks like. Fortunately, Infusion is easy to serve locally using the serve command:
npm run serve This will serve your working project from localhost:1313. Whenever you make changes to your files, the site will automatically rebuild. No need to refresh the web page!
Publishing on Github Pages Infusion creates a /docs folder containing the latest version of your site whenever you do an npm run build or a git commit.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Printing</title>
      <link>https://thepaciellogroup.github.io/infusion/patterns/printing/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thepaciellogroup.github.io/infusion/patterns/printing/</guid>
      <description>Infusion&amp;rsquo;s output site includes a one-page  Print version of the generated library, available at /print-version. So, if your library base URL is https://yourName.github.io/your-library, you can print the whole library — to PDF if wanted — from the following address:
https://yourName.github.io/your-library/print-version     Print styles are also provided for individual pattern pages so, if you wanted to print off a single pattern document, you can!
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Updating Infusion</title>
      <link>https://thepaciellogroup.github.io/infusion/patterns/updating/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thepaciellogroup.github.io/infusion/patterns/updating/</guid>
      <description>The core of Infusion&amp;rsquo;s functionality is in its Hugo theme, also called Infusion. This is found in the theme folder.
 content docs lib snippets static themes  infusion    Do not &amp;ldquo;hack the core&amp;rdquo;. If you have any issues with Infusion, please report them to the Infusion Github repository and they will be dealt with ASAP.
Infusion is undergoing constant development, so keep an eye out for new releases.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Advanced examples</title>
      <link>https://thepaciellogroup.github.io/infusion/patterns/advanced-examples/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thepaciellogroup.github.io/infusion/patterns/advanced-examples/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Basic examples</title>
      <link>https://thepaciellogroup.github.io/infusion/patterns/basic-examples/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thepaciellogroup.github.io/infusion/patterns/basic-examples/</guid>
      <description>&amp;lt;section&amp;gt; &amp;lt;h1&amp;gt;Heading&amp;lt;/h1&amp;gt; &amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Just some text&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt; &amp;lt;a href=&amp;quot;http://www.example.com/&amp;quot;&amp;gt;More…&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; &amp;lt;/section&amp;gt;   Level 1 folder  Level 2 file Level 2 folder  Level 3 file Level 3 folder  Level 4 file  Level 3 folder  Level 4 file Level 4 file  Level 3 file  Level 2 folder  Level 3 file Level 3 file Level 3 file  Level 2 file  Level 1 file     Launch in separate window   Great stuff Just some text</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Introduction</title>
      <link>https://thepaciellogroup.github.io/infusion/patterns/introduction/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thepaciellogroup.github.io/infusion/patterns/introduction/</guid>
      <description>Albos — an acronym for aria-labelledby On Steroids — is a (vanilla) JavaScript helper that makes it easier to associate an accessible name to page elements. Albos applies aria-labelledby attributes, but provides a more flexible and intuitive interface.
To learn more the accessible name computation, see (todo).
When to use? Please note that not all HTML elements can be given an accessible name using one of the ARIA labeling attributes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Syntax</title>
      <link>https://thepaciellogroup.github.io/infusion/patterns/syntax/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thepaciellogroup.github.io/infusion/patterns/syntax/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Welcome to Albos</title>
      <link>https://thepaciellogroup.github.io/infusion/patterns/welcome/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thepaciellogroup.github.io/infusion/patterns/welcome/</guid>
      <description>Eentje Tweetje You can just write markdown here. But don&amp;rsquo;t forget there are lots of shortcodes to help you with writing and showing off code too. See the documentation for Infusion for full details.
Drietje &amp;lt;body lang=&amp;quot;nl&amp;quot;&amp;gt; &amp;lt;/body&amp;gt;     Tested using   Firefox with JAWS   Safari   Safari iOS with Jaws   Edge       Here&amp;rsquo;s an example of a note shortcode for adding little &amp;ldquo;oh and also&amp;rdquo; notes to your patterns&amp;rsquo; documentation.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>